<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="date" content="2017-01-18T14:48:57Z"/>
<meta name="pdf:PDFVersion" content="1.4"/>
<meta name="access_permission:modify_annotations" content="true"/>
<meta name="access_permission:can_print_degraded" content="true"/>
<meta name="PDFVersion" content="1.4"/>
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2017-01-18T14:48:25Z"/>
<meta name="Last-Modified" content="2017-01-18T14:48:57Z"/>
<meta name="dcterms:modified" content="2017-01-18T14:48:57Z"/>
<meta name="dc:format" content="application/pdf; version=1.4"/>
<meta name="xmpMM:DocumentID" content="uuid:bef6877d-2574-4fbc-ad65-37e35325991f"/>
<meta name="Last-Save-Date" content="2017-01-18T14:48:57Z"/>
<meta name="access_permission:fill_in_form" content="true"/>
<meta name="pdf:docinfo:modified" content="2017-01-18T14:48:57Z"/>
<meta name="meta:save-date" content="2017-01-18T14:48:57Z"/>
<meta name="pdf:encrypted" content="false"/>
<meta name="modified" content="2017-01-18T14:48:57Z"/>
<meta name="pdf:docinfo:custom:PDFVersion" content="1.4"/>
<meta name="Content-Length" content="125280"/>
<meta name="Content-Type" content="application/pdf"/>
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser"/>
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.pdf.PDFParser"/>
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2017-01-18T14:48:25Z"/>
<meta name="created" content="Wed Jan 18 09:48:25 EST 2017"/>
<meta name="access_permission:extract_for_accessibility" content="true"/>
<meta name="access_permission:assemble_document" content="true"/>
<meta name="xmpTPg:NPages" content="9"/>
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2017-01-18T14:48:25Z"/>
<meta name="resourceName" content="bs1.pdf"/>
<meta name="access_permission:extract_content" content="true"/>
<meta name="access_permission:can_print" content="true"/>
<meta name="producer" content="Apache FOP Version 0.95"/>
<meta name="access_permission:can_modify" content="true"/>
<meta name="pdf:docinfo:producer" content="Apache FOP Version 0.95"/>
<meta name="pdf:docinfo:created" content="2017-01-18T14:48:25Z"/>
<title/>
</head>
<body><div class="page"><p/>
<p>Copyright 2017 CCC Information Services Inc. All Rights Reserved. Page 1 of 9
</p>
<p>Vehicle:  2015 Chevrolet Impala
.
</p>
<p>VIN:  2G1165S38F9293614
.
The report is compiled from multiple sources. It is not always possible for CCC to obtain
complete information on all vehicles. Therefore, there may be other information that applies
to the vehicle that is not reflected in this report. You should review the information and
supplement it as necessary when submitting a valuation request to CCC.
</p>
<p>Submission View OEM View 
. . .
. . .
</p>
<p>Legend
✓ - Equipment is currently selected in the valuation request.
std - Manufacturer indicates the equipment is standard.
avail - Manufacturer indicates the equipment is available.
inst - Manufacturer indicates the equipment is installed.
. - Manufacturer indicates the equipment is standard or installed, but the equipment is not
</p>
<p>currently selected in the valuation request.
</p>
<p>Note: The Installed indicator is only
available for companies that have
the necessary contract. Only select
manufacturers provide installed information.
</p>
<p>Original Prices MSRP Invoice
</p>
<p>Vehicle 1: 2015 Chevrolet Impala 4dr Sdn LTZ w/2LZ $35,440.00 $33,490.80
</p>
<p>* If multiple vehicles are listed, the VIN provided has multiple vehicle styles/trims for this model
</p>
<p>.&gt;
</p>
<p>.&gt;Transmission
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Automatic Transmission - inst ✓ Overdrive - inst 6 Speed Transmission 5 Speed Transmission
</p>
<p>.&gt; 4 Speed Transmission 3 Speed Transmission 4 Wheel Drive
</p>
<p>.&gt;
</p>
<p>.&gt;Power
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Power Steering - inst ✓ Power Brakes - inst ✓ Power Windows - inst ✓ Power Locks - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Power Mirrors - inst ✓ Heated Mirrors - inst ✓ Power Driver Seat - inst ✓ Power Passenger Seat - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Memory Package - inst Power Adjustable Pedals
</p>
<p>.&gt;
</p>
<p>.&gt;Decor
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Dual Mirrors - inst Body Side Moldings ✓ Tinted Glass - inst Aftermarket Film Tint
</p>
<p>.&gt; Privacy Glass Rear Power Sunshade ✓ Console/Storage - inst Overhead Console
</p>
<p>.&gt; Wood Interior Trim Woodgrain
</p>
<p>.&gt;</p>
<p/>
</div>
<div class="page"><p/>
<p>Copyright 2017 CCC Information Services Inc. All Rights Reserved. Page 2 of 9
</p>
<p>.&gt;Convenience
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Air Conditioning - inst ✓ Intermittent Wipers - inst ✓ Tilt Wheel - inst ✓ Cruise Control - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Rear Defogger - inst ✓ Keyless Entry - inst ✓ Alarm - inst ✓ Message Center - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Steering Wheel Touch Controls -
inst
</p>
<p>Rear Window Wiper ✓ Telescopic Wheel - inst ✓ Climate Control - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Navigation System - inst ✓ Remote Starter - inst Backup Camera w/ Parking
Sensors - inst
</p>
<p>✓ Parking Sensors
</p>
<p>.&gt; Entertainment Center Intelligent Cruise Dual Screen Entertainment ✓ Home Link - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;
</p>
<p>.&gt;Radio
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ AM Radio - inst ✓ FM Radio - inst ✓ Stereo - inst ✓ Search/Seek - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ CD Player - inst Cassette ✓ Auxiliary Audio Connection - inst✓ Premium Radio - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Satellite Radio - inst CD Changer/Stacker Equalizer
</p>
<p>.&gt;
</p>
<p>.&gt;Safety
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Drivers Side Air Bag - inst ✓ Passenger Air Bag - inst ✓ Anti-lock Brakes (4) - inst ✓ 4-Wheel Disc Brakes - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Front Side Impact Air Bags - inst ✓ Head/Curtain Air Bags - inst Positraction ✓ Communication System - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Hands Free Device - inst Anti-lock Brakes (2) ✓ Rear Side Impact Air Bags - inst Rollbar
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Blind Spot Detection - inst Heads Up Display Night Vision ✓ Lane Departure Warning - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;
</p>
<p>.&gt;Roof
</p>
<p>.&gt; Luggage/Roof Rack ✓ Electric Glass Roof - inst Electric Steel Roof Power Convertible Roof
</p>
<p>.&gt; Flip Roof ✓ Skyview Roof - inst Manual Steel Roof Vinyl Covered Roof
</p>
<p>.&gt; T-TOPS/PANEL Detachable Roof Dual Power Sunroofs Manual Glass Roof
</p>
<p>.&gt;
</p>
<p>.&gt;Seats
</p>
<p>.&gt; Cloth Seats ✓ Bucket Seats - inst Reclining/Lounge Seats ✓ Leather Seats - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt; 3rd Row Seat ✓ Heated Seats - inst Rear Heated Seats ✓ Ventilated Seats - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt; Power Third Seat
</p>
<p>.&gt;
</p>
<p>.&gt;Wheels
</p>
<p>.&gt; Styled Steel Wheels Full Wheel Covers Clad Wheels Aluminum/Alloy Wheels - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt; Chrome Wheels ✓ 20\" or Larger Wheels Wire Wheel Covers Wire Wheels
</p>
<p>.&gt; Locking Wheels
</p>
<p>.&gt;
</p>
<p>.&gt;Paint
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Clearcoat Paint - inst ✓ Metallic Paint - inst Two Tone Paint Three Stage Paint
</p>
<p>.&gt; Stone Guard
</p>
<p>.&gt;</p>
<p/>
</div>
<div class="page"><p/>
<p>Copyright 2017 CCC Information Services Inc. All Rights Reserved. Page 3 of 9
</p>
<p>.&gt;Other
</p>
<p>.&gt; Fog Lamps ✓ Traction Control - inst ✓ Stability Control - inst ✓ Rear Spoiler - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;✓ Signal Integrated Mirrors - inst Trailer Hitch ✓ Xenon Headlamps - inst Headlamp Washers
</p>
<p>.&gt; California Emissions ✓ Power Trunk/Gate Release - inst
</p>
<p>.&gt;
</p>
<p>Available Packages
</p>
<p>No packages available for this vehicle.</p>
<p/>
</div>
<div class="page"><p/>
<p>Copyright 2017 CCC Information Services Inc. All Rights Reserved. Page 4 of 9
</p>
<p>Vehicle:  2015 Chevrolet Impala
.
</p>
<p>VIN:  2G1165S38F9293614
.
The report is compiled from multiple sources. It is not always possible for CCC to obtain complete
information on all vehicles. Therefore, there may be other information that applies to the vehicle that
is not reflected in this report. You should review the information and supplement it as necessary when
submitting a valuation request to CCC.
</p>
<p>Submission View OEM View 
. . .
. . .
</p>
<p>Legend
OEM - Original Equipment Manufacturer
MSRP - Manufacturer Suggested Retail Price for equipment or packages
</p>
<p>Available Equipment
This section identifies all equipment and packages that were available at the time the vehicle was manufactured.
</p>
<p>MSRP OEM CODE EQUIPMENT
Installed $ 1050 C3U SUNROOF, POWER, TILT-SLIDING WITH ADDITIONAL SKYLIGHT FIXED GLASS AFT
</p>
<p>OF THE SLIDING GLASS
with power sunshade
</p>
<p>Installed $ 1035 PCH COMFORT AND CONVENIENCE PACKAGE
includes (KU1) ventilated driver seat, (KU3) ventilated front passenger seat, (UVD) heated
steering wheel, (N38) power tilt and telescoping steering column, (A45) driver seat, outside
mirrors and steering wheel memory settings, (UG1) Universal Home Remote, (B58) premium
carpeted front and rear floor mats, (B36) carpeted trunk mat, (DD8) auto-dimming inside
rearview mirror and (DLG) outside heated power-adjustable mirrors with turn signal indicators,
ground illumination and driver-side auto-dimming feature
</p>
<p>Installed $ 650 PCJ PREMIUM AUDIO PACKAGE
includes (UQS) Bose premium surround sound 11-speaker system and (KI6) 120-volt power
outlet
</p>
<p>Installed $ 495 IO6 AUDIO SYSTEM, CHEVROLET MYLINK RADIO WITH NAVIGATION, AM/FM STEREO
AND CD PLAYER
</p>
<p>Installed $ 425 SB2 LPO, REAR SPOILER
Installed $ 400 RQ9 WHEELS, 20" (50.9 CM) ALUMINUM
Installed $ 15 VK3 LICENSE PLATE BRACKET, FRONT
Installed $ - FE9 EMISSIONS, FEDERAL REQUIREMENTS
Installed $ - LFX ENGINE, 3.6L DOHC V6 DI WITH VARIABLE VALVE TIMING (VVT)
</p>
<p>(305 hp [227.4 kW] @ 6800 rpm, 264 lb-ft of torque [356.4 N-m] @ 5200 rpm)
(Includes E85 FlexFuel capability with (FE9) Federal emissions or (YF5/NE1 and NC7)
California emissions with the Federal override only.)
</p>
<p>Installed $ - M7W TRANSMISSION, 6-SPEED AUTOMATIC, ELECTRONICALLY-CONTROLLED WITH
OVERDRIVE
</p>
<p>Installed $ - 2LZ LTZ PREFERRED EQUIPMENT GROUP</p>
<p/>
</div>
<div class="page"><p/>
<p>Copyright 2017 CCC Information Services Inc. All Rights Reserved. Page 5 of 9
</p>
<p>includes Standard Equipment
Installed $ - RAL TIRES, P245/40R20 ALL-SEASON, BLACKWALL
Installed $ - G7P RED ROCK METALLIC
Installed $ - A51 SEATS, FRONT BUCKET
Installed $ - H0Y JET BLACK, LEATHER-APPOINTED SEAT TRIM
Installed $ - DLG MIRRORS, OUTSIDE HEATED POWER-ADJUSTABLE
</p>
<p>manual-folding with integrated turn signal indicators, ground illumination, driver-side auto-
dimming feature and chrome mirror caps
</p>
<p>Installed $ - UQS AUDIO SYSTEM FEATURE, BOSE CENTERPOINT SURROUND SOUND PREMIUM 11-
SPEAKER SYSTEM, SOUND-STAGE SIGNAL PROCESSING
</p>
<p>Installed $ - KU1 SEAT, VENTILATED DRIVER
Installed $ - KU3 SEAT, VENTILATED PASSENGER, FRONT
Installed $ - B58 FLOOR MATS, PREMIUM CARPETED FRONT AND REAR
Installed $ - N38 STEERING COLUMN, POWER TILT AND TELESCOPIC
Installed $ - UVD STEERING WHEEL, HEATED
Installed $ - A45 DRIVER MEMORY
</p>
<p>recalls 2 driver "presets" for 8-way power driver seat, tilt/telescoping steering column and outside
mirrors
</p>
<p>Installed $ - UG1 UNIVERSAL HOME REMOTE
includes garage door opener, 3-channel programmable
</p>
<p>Installed $ - KI6 POWER OUTLET, 120-VOLT, LOCATED ON THE REAR OF CENTER CONSOLE
Installed $ - DD8 MIRROR, INSIDE REARVIEW AUTO-DIMMING
Installed $ - B36 TRUNK MAT, CARPETED
</p>
<p>$ - NE1 EMISSIONS, CONNECTICUT, DELAWARE, MAINE, MARYLAND, MASSACHUSETTS,
NEW JERSEY, NEW YORK, OREGON, PENNSYLVANIA, RHODE ISLAND, VERMONT
AND WASHINGTON STATE REQUIREMENTS
</p>
<p>$ - YF5 EMISSIONS, CALIFORNIA STATE REQUIREMENTS
$ - NB8 EMISSIONS OVERRIDE, CALIFORNIA
</p>
<p>(allows a dealer in states that require California emissions - California, Connecticut, Delaware,
Maryland, Massachusetts, New Jersey, New York, Oregon, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island or
Washington - to order Federal emissions for a vehicle that will be registered in a state that has
Federal emission requirements).
</p>
<p>$ - NC7 EMISSIONS OVERRIDE, FEDERAL
(for vehicles ordered by dealers in Federal emission states with (YF5) or (NE1) emissions - Not
required for vehicles being shipped to California, Connecticut, Delaware, Maine, Maryland,
Massachusetts, New Jersey, New York, Oregon, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, Vermont or
Washington)
</p>
<p>$ - NB9 EMISSIONS OVERRIDE, STATE-SPECIFIC
(for dealers ordering vehicles in (YF5) or (NE1) emission states - California, Connecticut,
Delaware, Maine, Maryland, Massachusetts, New Jersey, New York, Oregon, Pennsylvania,
Rhode Island, Vermont and Washington)
</p>
<p>$ - Q6M WHEELS, 19" (48.3 CM) MACHINED-FACE ALUMINUM
$ - Q2B TIRES, P245/45R19 ALL-SEASON, BLACKWALL
$ - GAN SILVER ICE METALLIC
$ - G1M BLUE VELVET METALLIC
$ - GBA BLACK
$ 395 GBE CRYSTAL RED TINTCOAT
$ - GLJ ASHEN GRAY METALLIC
$ - GWT CHAMPAGNE SILVER METALLIC
$ 995 G1W IRIDESCENT PEARL TRICOAT
$ - GWS SILVER TOPAZ METALLIC</p>
<p/>
</div>
<div class="page"><p/>
<p>Copyright 2017 CCC Information Services Inc. All Rights Reserved. Page 6 of 9
</p>
<p>$ - STANDARD PAINT
$ - H1P JET BLACK/MOJAVE, LEATHER-APPOINTED SEAT TRIM
$ - H1Q JET BLACK/DARK TITANIUM, LEATHER-APPOINTED SEAT TRIM
$ - IO5 AUDIO SYSTEM, CHEVROLET MYLINK RADIO, AM/FM STEREO WITH CD PLAYER
$ 200 PDH LPO, ALL-WEATHER MAT PROTECTION PACKAGE
</p>
<p>includes (VAV) Premium all-weather Black front and rear floor mats, LPO and (VLI) Premium
all-weather cargo mat, LPO.
</p>
<p>$ 75 K05 ENGINE BLOCK HEATER
$ 2200 5XQ LPO, 19" (48.3 CM) ALUMINUM WHEELS, DESIGN 3
$ 115 SFE LPO, WHEEL LOCKS
$ 595 VAT LPO, BODY-COLOR SURROUND GRILLE
$ 140 VAV LPO, PREMIUM ALL-WEATHER FLOOR MATS, FRONT AND REAR, BLACK
$ 1195 KSG CRUISE CONTROL, ADAPTIVE, FULL RANGE
</p>
<p>with collision mitigation braking
$ 170 VEB LPO, PEDAL COVER SET
$ 140 RVW LPO, TRUNK ORGANIZER
$ 80 VLI LPO, PREMIUM ALL-WEATHER CARGO MAT
$ - ROV ONSTAR WITH 4G LTE FOR FLEET (12GB/12 MONTHS)
</p>
<p>provides a built-in Wi-Fi hotspot to connect to the internet at 4G LTE speeds, includes AT&amp;T
12GB data plan good for 12 months.
</p>
<p>$ - ROW ONSTAR WITH 4G LTE FOR FLEET (24GB/24 MONTHS)
provides a built-in Wi-Fi hotspot to connect to the internet at 4G LTE speeds, includes AT&amp;T
24GB data plan good for 24 months.
</p>
<p>$ - R8G ONSTAR 1 ADDITIONAL YEAR OF ONSTAR SAFE AND SOUND SERVICE.
Provides 1 year of Safe and Sound service in addition to the 6 months of standard Directions and
Connections service (12 months for Cadillac) that is included in the price of the vehicle. Total
service duration is 18 months (24 months for Cadillac).
</p>
<p>$ - R8W ONSTAR 2 ADDITIONAL YEARS OF ONSTAR SAFE AND SOUND SERVICE.
Provides 2 years of Safe and Sound service in addition to the 6 months of standard Directions and
Connections service (12 months for Cadillac) that is included in the price of the vehicle. Total
service duration is 30 months (36 months for Cadillac).
</p>
<p>$ - R8P ONSTAR 30 ADDITIONAL MONTHS OF ONSTAR SAFE AND SOUND SERVICE.
Provides 30 months of Safe and Sound service in addition to the 6 months of standard Directions
and Connections service that is included in the price of the vehicle. Total service duration is 36
months.
</p>
<p>$ - R8Y ONSTAR 1 ADDITIONAL YEAR OF ONSTAR DIRECTIONS AND CONNECTIONS
SERVICE.
Provides 1 year of Directions and Connections service in addition to the 6 months of standard
Directions and Connections service (12 months for Cadillac) that is included in the price of the
vehicle. Total service duration is 18 months (24 months for Cadillac).
</p>
<p>$ - R8Z ONSTAR 2 ADDITIONAL YEARS OF ONSTAR DIRECTIONS AND CONNECTIONS
SERVICE.
Provides 2 years of Directions and Connections service in addition to the 6 months of standard
Directions and Connections service (12 months for Cadillac) that is included in the price of the
vehicle. Total service duration is 30 months (36 months for Cadillac).
</p>
<p>$ - RFG ONSTAR 30 ADDITIONAL MONTHS OF ONSTAR DIRECTIONS AND CONNECTIONS
SERVICE.
Provides 30 months of Directions and Connections service in addition to the 6 months of standard
Directions and Connections service that is included in the price of the vehicle. Total service
duration is 36 months.
</p>
<p>$ - RFH ONSTAR 42 ADDITIONAL MONTHS OF ONSTAR SAFE AND SOUND SERVICE.</p>
<p/>
</div>
<div class="page"><p/>
<p>Copyright 2017 CCC Information Services Inc. All Rights Reserved. Page 7 of 9
</p>
<p>Provides 42 months of Safe and Sound service in addition to the 6 months of standard Directions
and Connections service that is included in the price of the vehicle. Total service duration is 48
months.
</p>
<p>$ -135 R9Y FLEET FREE MAINTENANCE CREDIT
This option code provides a credit in lieu of the free oil changes, tire rotations and inspections
(4 maximum), during the first 24 months and 24,000 miles period for this ordered vehicle. The
invoice will detail the applicable credit. The customer will be responsible for all oil change, tire
rotations and inspections costs for this vehicle.
</p>
<p>Standard Equipment
</p>
<p>.
MECHANICAL
Engine, 3.6L DOHC V6 DI with Variable Valve Timing (VVT) (305 hp [227.4 kW] @ 6800 rpm, 264 lb-ft of torque [356.4 N-m] @ 5200 rpm)
(Includes E85 FlexFuel capability with (FE9) Federal emissions or (YF5/NE1 and NC7) California emissions with the Federal override only.)
Transmission, 6-speed automatic, electronically-controlled with overdrive
Axle, 2.77 final drive ratio
Front wheel drive
Battery, 70AH, maintenance free with rundown protection, heavy-duty 512 cold-cranking amps
Chassis equipment, front strut assembly
Suspension, rear 4-link
Steering, power, variable assist, electric
Brakes, 4-wheel antilock, 4-wheel disc
Brake lining, high-performance, noise and dust performance with FNC rotors
Exhaust, dual-outlet stainless-steel with bright tips integrated in fascia
.
EXTERIOR
Wheels, 19" (48.3 cm) machined-face aluminum
Tires, P245/45R19 all-season, blackwall
Wheel, compact spare, 17" (43.2 cm) steel
Tire, compact spare, T125/70R17
Headlamps, high intensity discharge
Glass, acoustic, laminated front-side and windshield
Mirrors, outside heated power-adjustable manual-folding with integrated turn signal indicators and ground illumination (Chrome mirror caps.)
Wipers, front intermittent
Door handles, chrome with body-color strip
.
ENTERTAINMENT
Audio system, Chevrolet MyLink Radio, AM/FM stereo with CD player
Audio system feature, 6-speaker system 100-watt
Audio system feature, 8" diagonal color infotainment display, touch-screen, motorized power up/down with hidden storage and valet password
lock
Audio system feature, SD card receptacle
Audio system feature, USB ports, 3; 2 located inside floor console, 1 behind radio touch-screen
SiriusXM Satellite Radio is standard on nearly all 2015 GM models. Enjoy a 3-month All Access trial subscription with over 150 channels
including commercial-free music, plus sports, news and entertainment. Plus you can listen to SiriusXM Internet Radio everywhere on your
computer, smartphone or tablet. Welcome to the world of SiriusXM. (IMPORTANT: The SiriusXM Satellite Radio trial package is not provided
on vehicles that are ordered for Fleet Daily Rental ("FDR") use. If you decide to continue listening after your trial, the subscription plan you
choose will automatically renew and you will be charged according to your chosen payment method at then-current rates. Fees and taxes
apply. To cancel you must call us at 1-866-635-2349. See our Customer Agreement for complete terms at www.siriusxm.com. All fees and
programming subject to change.)</p>
<p/>
</div>
<div class="page"><p/>
<p>Copyright 2017 CCC Information Services Inc. All Rights Reserved. Page 8 of 9
</p>
<p>Bluetooth for phone, streaming audio for music for select phones
Steering wheel controls, mounted audio and cruise controls
.
INTERIOR
Seats, front bucket
Seat trim, leather-appointed
Seats, heated driver and front passenger
Seat adjuster, driver 8-way power
Seat adjuster, front passenger 8-way power
Seat adjuster, driver power lumbar
Seat adjuster, front passenger power lumbar
Seat, rear 60/40 split-folding
Head restraints, 4-way adjustable, up/down, fore/aft, front
Head restraints, rear, adjustable, folding
Console, floor, uplevel with covered storage
Storage, innovative, hidden behind 8" diagonal touch screen with valet-mode lockable, rear armrest, front and rear door panels, reconfigurable
console with removable cup holders, dedicated umbrella storage in front door and hidden storage in trunk
Armrest, rear center
Floor mats, carpeted front
Floor mats, carpeted rear
Steering column, manual tilt and telescopic
Steering wheel, 4-spoke leather-wrapped
Instrumentation, analog with speedometer, tachometer, engine temperature and fuel gauge with color Driver Information Center
Driver Information Center, color display includes trip/fuel information, vehicle information and vehicle messages
Compass display, located in the Driver Information Center
Window, power with driver Express-Up and Down
Windows, power with Express-Down on all
Headlamp control, automatic on and off
Keyless Access, passive entry
Keyless start, push button
Remote vehicle starter system
Cruise control, electronic with set and resume speed
Trunk release, power located inside on instrument panel left of steering wheel
Trunk opening touch pad
Theft-deterrent system
Air conditioning, dual-zone automatic climate control with individual climate settings for driver and front passenger
Vent, rear console, air
Defogger, rear-window
Power outlets, 2, auxiliary, 12-volt located on front of console and inside console
Power outlet, auxiliary, 12-volt located forward of console, below the HVAC controls
Map pockets, driver and front passenger seatbacks
Mirror, inside rearview manual day/night
Visors, driver and front passenger illuminated vanity mirrors
Assist handles, driver, front passenger and rear outboard
Shift knob, leather-wrapped
Brake, park, electronic push button powered located on instrument panel left of steering wheel
Cargo convenience net, trunk
Lighting, interior with theater dimming, delayed entry/exit, glovebox and trunk
Lamp, interior, ambient, door
Lamp, interior, ambient instrument panel
.</p>
<p/>
</div>
<div class="page"><p/>
<p>Copyright 2017 CCC Information Services Inc. All Rights Reserved. Page 9 of 9
</p>
<p>SAFETY
Brake Assist, panic
Brake control, cornering
StabiliTrak, stability control system
Traction control
Daytime Running Lamps, upper and lower auxiliary, LED
Air bags, 10 total, frontal and knee for driver and front passenger, side-impact seat-mounted and roof rail for front and rear outboard seating
positions includes Passenger Sensing System (Always use safety belts and child restraints. Children are safer when properly secured in a rear seat
in the appropriate child restraint. See the Owner's Manual for more information.)
OnStar Directions and Connections plan for 6 months including Automatic Crash Response, Stolen Vehicle Assistance, Roadside Assistance
and Turn-by-Turn Navigation (Visit www.onstar.com for vehicle availability, details and system limitations. Services may vary by model and
conditions.)
OnStar Basic plan for 5 years including RemoteLink Key Fob Services, OnStar Vehicle Diagnostics and Dealer Maintenance Notification
(Access is available for 5 years from the date of vehicle delivery, and is transferable. Does not include emergency services. To cancel
RemoteLink Key Fob Services or if your vehicle is sold, contact an OnStar Advisor. See www.onstar.com/mobile for full details.)
OnStar with 4G LTE provides a built-in Wi-Fi hotspot to connect to the internet at 4G LTE speeds (Visit www.onstar.com for vehicle
availability, details and system limitations. Services and connectivity may vary by model and conditions. 4G LTE service available in select
markets. 4G LTE performance based on industry averages and vehicle systems design. Some services require data plan.)
Rear Vision Camera
Rear Cross-Traffic Alert
Forward Collision Alert
Lane Departure Warning
Side Blind Zone Alert
Rear Park Assist
Safety belts, 3-point, all positions
Safety belt pretensioners, driver and front passenger
Door and window locks, rear child security, power
LATCH system (Lower Anchors and Top tethers for CHildren) for child safety seats
Tire Pressure Monitor
Tool kit, road emergency</p>
<p/>
</div>
</body></html>